ASIM HOSKINS

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Talented Manager with expert team leadership, planning and organizational skills built during successful career. Smoothly equip employees to independently handle daily functions and meet customer needs. Diligent trainer and mentor with exceptional management abilities and results-driven approach.

WORK HISTORY

Manager, 09/2023 - Current Culver's Restaurant, Minot, ND

- Managed and motivated over 20 employees to be productive and engaged in work.
- Accomplished multiple tasks within established timeframes.
- Maintained professional, organized, and safe environment for employees and patrons.
- Enhanced customer satisfaction by resolving disputes promptly, maintaining open lines of communication, and ensuring highquality service delivery.
- Resolved staff member conflicts, actively listening to concerns and finding appropriate middle ground.
- Cross-trained existing employees to maximize team agility and performance.
- Built high-performing teams at both stores through effective recruitment, onboarding, and talent development initiatives.
- Creation of the work schedule on a week to week basis.

Assistant Store Manager, 05/2016 - 09/2023 Culver's Restaurant, Michigan City, IN

- Managed cash registers efficiently, ensuring accurate transactions, balancing drawers daily, and minimizing discrepancies.
- Managed opening and closing procedures and recommended changes to enhance efficiency of daily activities.
- Enhanced store appearance for increased sales by maintaining cleanliness and implementing strategic merchandise displays.
- Rotated merchandise and displays to feature new products and promotions.
- Walked through store areas to identify and proactively resolve issues negatively impacting operations.
- Mentored new employees on company policies, procedures, and best practices to ensure their success within the organization.
- Supervised and evaluated staff to help improve skills, achieve daily objectives, and attain advancement.

Minot, ND 58701

2192848776

asimhoskins02@gmail.com

Bold Profile

WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

https://github.com/ThaAmateur

SKILLS

Team Leadership

Computer Skills

Policy Implementation

Cross-Functional Teamwork

Project Management

Staff Management

Staff Training and Development

Complex Problem-Solving

Verbal and written communication

Time Management

Team Leadership

- Fostered positive work culture by promoting teamwork and recognizing individual achievements among staff members regularly.
- Implemented innovative programs to increase employee loyalty and reduce turnover.
- Recruited, hired, and trained initial personnel, working to establish key internal functions and outline scope of positions for new organization.
- Reported issues to higher management with great detail.
- Observed each employee's individual strengths and initiated mentoring program to improve areas of weakness.
- Monitored daily cash discrepancies, inventory shrinkage and driveoff.
- Handled problematic customers and clients to assist lower-level employees and maintain excellent customer service.\
- Created a training program from the ground up for that store, which allowed for growth from talented employees.
- Closely mangaged a team of 8 team trainers and coordinated cross training between employee's and managers.
- Created the schedule on a week to week basis.

Front Desk Consultation Agent, 06/2022 - 01/2023 Best Buy, Valparaiso, IN

- Assessed client requirements thoroughly to create customized action plans aligned with their goals and objectives.
- Built rapport quickly and persuaded customers to buy without applying pressure.
- Set up appointments for clients to have repairs done.
- Assisted in repairs of client devices.

EDUCATION

No Degree, Computer Science And Programming

Ivy Tech - Michigan City

• 3.0 GPA

No Degree, Computer Science And Programming

Purdue NorthWest - Westville, IN

• 3.2 GPA

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Currently in the process of learning multiple coding languages for a future in the tech industry. As of right now, I am learning JavaScript, NextJS, and React. I am planning to go back to college to finish my degree in Computer Science.

REFERENCES

Derrick Miller 701-240-2771

- Zak Chapplle 219-210-1632
- Hannah Yerensian 219-214-6338